Vishant Sharma

Software Engineer

Phone: 9997871677

8.6/10.0

Email: vishantsharma0001@amail.com

Address: Shamli, India

Date of Birth: 19/May/2001

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/vishant-sharma-01/

Result-oriented, resourceful and problem-solving software engineer specializing in large-scale software design and development for a wide variety of industries. High level of involvement in the advancement of the industry experience

and adherence to best practices.	, , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , , ,
EDUCATION	
B.Tech ► Dr. APJ Abdul Kalam Technical University 7.32/10.0	Aug 2017 - Aug 2021
Intermediate ► Central Board of Secondry Education(CBSE), Shamli 52%	Apr 2015 - Jun 2017
Matriculation ► Central Board of Secondry Education(CBSE)	Apr 2013 - Mar 2015

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer Trainee ► Adeptia, Noida

Oct 2021 - Apr 2022

- Responsible for various solutions Like designing Data mapping, Process Flow & Layout
- Work for API integration with different security policies
- Worked on Electric data interchange (EDI), ETL and Data Integration.
- Worked on Salesforce integration.
- Created Data mappings with logical rules.
- Created Inbound and Outbound transactions and Process flows for different versions of EDI.
- Worked on web services and securities

Software Engineer ► Adeptia, Noida

Apr 2022 - Present

Worked on American Air Filter Project.

- Implement the Inbound and Outbound transactions with logical rule mapping and parse the EDI data to IDoc in XML format or vice versa
- Implement process flow to parse the data from LAN location to SAP server with the help of a script that will be written
 in JAVA.
- Integrate the data from the SAP server to the LAN location and vice versa.

SKILLS

Algorithm | Data Structure | JAVA | Jakarta EE | Azure | Kubernetes | Docker | Ansible | Jenkins | Linux | Github | Git | MYSQL | Oracle DB | HTML | CSS | Bootstrap | Microservices | Electronic Data Interchange | Data Integration | Team Management | Work Management | Work Planning

PROJECTS

American Air Filter Project (03/2022)

- Implement the Inbound and Outbound transactions with logical rule mapping and parse the EDI data to IDoc in XML format or vice versa.
- Implement process flow to parse the data from LAN location to SAP server with the help of a script that will be written in IAVA
- Integrate the data from the SAP server to the LAN location and vice versa.
- Technology stack: EDI, SAP Server, Java.
- Tools: Adeptia ETL Tool, Notepad++.



AUTO INSURANCE (02/2021 - 05/2021)

- This Auto Insurance project is a web-based application.
- All the information and data catch up which providing any insurance policy to any company.
- Frontend: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, JSP
- Backend: Java, Servlet, MYSQL.
- Server: Apache Tomcat server.
- IDE: Eclipse (2020-12)

MartSol App (10/10/2020-08/11/2020)

- MartSol app allows to buy any product at low prices
- Users can easily search for any product.
- Design of this app is user-friendly so that users don't face
- any difficulty to use this app.
- Technology Stack: Java(swing), MYSQL.
- **IDE:** Apache NetBeans

NETWORK PACKET SNIFFER (20/11/2020-15/02/2021)

- It's a desktop application that is a packet analyser software that monitors network traffic.
- Using this application admin of the system can capture network packets.
- Technology Stack: Java(swing)
- IDE: Apache NetBeans

A /	CHI	1-1	I = V	EN	ITC
A	СΠ	IE V			пэ

Qualified AMCAT (08/2021)

Web Development Training Certificate by Internshala

Java SE Training Certificate by INCAPP

Java EE Training Certificate by INCAPP

Spring Framework Certificate by INCAPP

LANGUAGES

Hindi | English

INTERESTS

Gaming, Riding, Coding